电视机:这里是19频道,长岛新闻…….
TV: Channel nineteen, Long Island News...
麦琪:还有五分钟,克莉丝,然后去睡觉.
Maggie: Five more minutes, Chrissy, then bed time.
克莉丝:哦,真不错!
Chrissy: Oh, great!For the first time I'm drawing inside the lines,
第一次这么有兴趣来画画,我就必须去睡觉了.
I've got to go to bed.
本:克莉丝,提醒你;妈妈说话算话.相信我,绝对错不了.
Ben: Chrissy, a tip; Mom's a sucker for cute.Trust me, it never fails.
麦琪:好了,本,把这些拿到你房间,然后开始做家庭作业.
Maggie: OK, Ben, take these to your room and get started on your homework.
本:该死,妈妈!我惊呆了.你真是个漂亮女人.
Ben: Godzooks, Mom!I can't move.You are one beautiful woman.
麦琪:赶快,先生.
Maggie: Hustle mister.
本:我知道说"该死"错了.
Ben: I knew "Godzooks" was wrong.
迈克:妈妈,快点,我约会快要迟到了,但没有一件干净衬衫.
Mike: Mom, quick, I'm late for a date and I don't have a clean shirt.
麦琪:哦,迈克,
Maggie: Oh, Mike, we've been over this more times than I care to remember.
我们已经解决这种事情的次数要比我记得的次数还要多.你的衣服你自己洗.
You do your own laundry.
迈克:妈妈!你变年轻了?
Mike: Mom!Are you getting younger?
麦琪:年轻!
Maggie: Younger!
迈克:我是说,我所能说的是,妈呀!
Mike: I mean all I can say is, holy moly!
麦琪:穿你爸爸的衬衣.
Maggie: Take your Dad's shirt.
迈克:哦,不是他的好衬衫?
Mike: Oh, not his good one?
麦琪:为什么不是?
Maggie: Why not?
迈克:哦,好!谢谢你,妈妈.
Mike: Oh, yes!Thank you, Mom.
克莉丝:天哪,摸起来真好.
Chrissy: Holy moly was a nice touch.
迈克:谢谢.
Mike: Thanks.
克莉丝:你知道,你看起来就像那喜欢讲催眠故事的人.
Chrissy: You know, you look like the kind of guy who would enjoy a good
怎么样,老鼠先生找到了家?
bed-time story.How about, Mr.Mouse finds a home?
迈克:啊……呃……对不起,克莉丝,但是……呃……迈克先生找到了一个金发美女.嗨,
Mike: Ah...err...sorry Chrissy, but...err...Mr.Mike found a blond.
听好,开萝尔去哪了?也许他可以给你读催眠故事.
Hey listen, where's Carol?Maybe she can read you a bed-time story.
克莉丝:她出去约会了.
Chrissy: She's out on a date.
迈克:不,说真的,她在哪?
Mike: No, really where is she?
克莉丝:是真的.
Chrissy: It's true.
迈克:哦,那么,最终证明那大脚活着.
Mike: Oh, well, finally proof that Bigfoot lives.
克莉丝:他活着!你能带我见他吗?
Chrissy: He does!Will you take me to meet him?
迈克:不,不,克莉丝,我在开玩笑,这只是一个笑话.
Mike: No, no, Chrissy, I'm kidding, it was just a joke.
克莉丝:这本书不长,迈克.而且印刷的字体非常大.
Chrissy: It's not a long book, Mike.And the print's pretty big.
迈克:对不起,克莉丝,但是我不能让一个金发美女等我吧.
Mike: I'm sorry, Chrissy, but I can't keep a blond waiting.
克莉丝:那好吧,请她过来.绝大多数女性喜欢老鼠先生.
Chrissy: Well, invite her over.Most women love Mr.Mouse.
迈克:对不起,克莉丝,但我不能.我走了.再见.
Mike: I'm sorry Chrissy, but I can't.I gotta go.See ya.
克莉丝:啊!!哦,对不起.
Chrissy: Aarrgghh!!Well, I'm sorry.I've never seen a six foot mouse before.
我之前从来没有见过六脚老鼠.你说什么呢,来到泽西.
What do you mean, come to Jersey.
开萝尔:诺曼,我今晚过的很愉快.
Carol: Norman, I had a wonderful time tonight.
诺曼:开萝尔,
Norman: Carol, you are the first girl I've met,
你是我见到的第一个不介意乘垃圾车出去的女孩.
who doesn't mind going out in a garbage truck.
开萝尔:这是垃圾车?
Carol: Is this a garbage truck?
诺曼:你想再次发动?
Norman: Do you wanna pull the lever again?
开萝尔:不,太吵了.你想进来喝杯咖啡吗?
Carol: No, it's too noisy.Would you like to come in for some coffee?
诺曼:当然.我想喝咖啡.
Norman: Sure.I don't want coffee.
开萝尔:我也不.
Carol: Neither do I.
克莉丝:嗨,开萝尔!
Chrissy: Hi, Carol!
开萝尔:克莉丝,这时候你出来在这干什么?
Carol: Chrissy, what are you doing out here at this hour?
克莉丝:不是亲吻垃圾工.
Chrissy: Not kissing the garbage man.
开萝尔:克莉丝,睡觉去.你在侵犯我的隐私.
Carol: Chissy, go to bed.You are invading our privacy.
克莉丝:去吻别人吧,那里我们没有野餐.
Chrissy: Then go kiss someone else, where we're not having a picnic.
开萝尔:我们!谁在野餐呢?
Carol: We!Who's having a picnic?
克莉丝:我和我的朋友.你叫什么名字?艾克.
Chrissy: Me and my friend!What's your name?Ike.
开萝尔:谁是艾克?他在哪?
Carol: Who is Ike?Where is this kid?
克莉丝:小心!你几乎踩到它的尾巴了.
Chrissy: Watch it!You almost stepped on his tail.
开萝尔:尾巴!
Carol: Tail!
克莉丝:是呀,艾克是只老鼠!
Chrissy: Yeah, Ike's a mouse!
诺曼:这个小孩精神不正常.
Norman: Little babe's bonkers.
克莉丝:再说这样的脏话,他会咬你脖子.
Chrissy: One more crack like that, he'll bite you on the neck!
开萝尔:诺玛,就当她不存在.她只是个小……啤酒!你把啤酒拿到这干什么?
Carol: Norman, just ignore her.She's just a little...beer!What's beer doing out here?
克莉丝:放松点,为艾克准备的.可以让它吃奶酪更顺畅.
Chrissy: Relax, it's just for Ike.It makes the cheese go down smoother.
开萝尔:克莉丝,我不希望听到有关这个看不到的老鼠的胡话.
Carol: Chrissy, I don't wanna hear any more nonsense about this invisible mouse.
克莉丝:你看不见他?
Chrissy: You don't see him?
开萝尔:看不见.
Carol: No.
克莉丝:他在盯着你看.你这个家伙,在盯着你看.
Chrissy: He's staring at you.Boy, is he staring at you.
诺曼:你知道的,开萝尔,也许今晚就到此结束吧.
Norman: You know, Carol, maybe we should call it a night.
开萝尔:我可以再见你吗?
Carol: Will I see you again?
诺曼:周二和周四!在路边!
Norman: Tuesdays and Thursdays!Be on the curb!
克莉丝:艾克说别担心.他说他想将来能够带像你这样的小妞出去.
Chrissy: Mike says not to worry.He says he's like to take a babe out like you some time.
开萝尔:妈妈,爸爸,起来!
Carol: Mom, Dad, wake up!
麦琪:什么事呀?
Maggie: What?
开萝尔:克莉丝正在车道上,让一个她假想的老鼠喝啤酒.晚安.
Carol: Chrissy, is on the driveway letting an imaginary mouse have a beer.Goodnight.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
杰森:开萝尔,回来.再说一遍.
Jason: Carol, come back.Say what you said again.
开萝尔:克莉丝在外面让一个她假想的老鼠喝啤酒.
Carol: Chrissy was outside letting an imaginary mouse have a beer.
杰森:有你说的这回事.
Jason: That's what I thought you said.
开萝尔:别担心,我已经把啤酒倒了,然后使克莉丝睡觉了.
Carol: Don't worry, I poured the beer out and put Chrissy to bed.
麦琪:那么你处理好了?
Maggie: So you handled it?
开萝尔:是的.不客气.
Carol: Yes.And you're welcome.
杰森:开萝尔,如果你已经处理好了,那么你为什么把我们叫醒?
Jason: Carol, if you handled it, why are you waking us up?
开萝尔:是这样,她毁掉了我的约会,那么我就想毁掉你们的觉.
Carol: Well, she ruined my date, so I wanted to ruin your evening.
麦琪:哦!
Maggie: Oh!
杰森:还有一件事,顺便说一下,是关于这个约会的;难道通常不是我们先见见男孩子?
Jason: That's another thing, by the way, about this date; don't we usually get to meet the guy first?
开萝尔:是这样,你们已经见过.每周二和周四,在路边.
Carol: Well, you have.Every Tuesday and Thursday on the curb.
杰森:你是在和我们的垃圾工约会?
Jason: Are you dating our garbage man?
麦琪:杰森,诺曼不仅仅是个垃圾工.
Maggie: Jason, Norman isn't just a garbage man.
他是个专业的健美运动员,他还爱好诗歌,
He's a professional body-builder who likes poetry, quiet walks,
安静走路,听话的女人和甲壳类动物.
women who listen and shellfish.
杰森:这里发生了什么,当我在工作的时候?
Jason: What goes on around here while I'm at work?
开萝尔:爸爸,忘掉我的约会吧.你的小女儿正在幻觉中.
Carol: Dad, forget my date.Your younger daughter is hallucinating.
麦琪:哦,开萝尔,你在说些什么呢?
Maggie: Oh, Carol, what are you talking about?
杰森:难道你不认为"幻觉"这词用的有点重?
Jason: Don't you think "hallucinate" is a bit strong?
开萝尔:我不认为.在她的老鼠把诺曼赶走之后……他就离我而去了.
Carol: I don't think so.After her mouse drove Norman away...he was checking me out.
杰森:我们在这里说谁的幻觉呢?哈哈.我们这是在说谁的幻觉啊?哈哈.布德科利尔
Jason: Who's imagination are we dealing with here?Ha ha.Bud Collier.
麦琪:说什么.
Maggie: Excuse me.
杰森:我虚幻中的朋友.布德科利尔.记着吗?大型演出的主办者,哦,是五十场的演出.他曾经创作了"真相","敲打的时钟"
Jason: That was my imaginary friend.Bud Collier.Remember, big game show host...oh all the big shows of the fifties.He used to do "Tell the Truth", "Beat the clock".
麦琪:杰森,我知道他是谁了.
Maggie: Jason, I know who he was.
杰森:不错,当我还是克莉丝这么大的时候,
Jason: Yeah, when I was Chrissy's age, I'd pretend he'd come over to visit.
我装着他来看望我.他猜我的职业.每次都猜对.
He used to guess my occupation.Got it right every time.
麦琪:晚安,小甜心.
Maggie: Good night, sweetheart.
杰森:噢.
Jason: Well.
麦琪:,噢,什么?
Maggie: Well, what?
杰森:那么谁是你虚的朋友?
Jason: Well, who was your imaginary friend?
麦琪:杰森,很晚了.
Maggie: Jason, it's late.
杰森:哦,快点,麦琪.我们结婚这么些年,你还没有告诉我谁是你虚幻的朋友.虽然我知道你的每件事情,包括你右大腿内侧的胎记.
Jason: Oh, come on, Maggie.We've been married all these years, you've never told me who your imaginary friend is.And I know every thing about you, including that mole on your inner right thigh.
麦琪:啊!我右大腿内侧没有胎记.
Maggie: Ah!I don't have a mole on my inner right thigh.
杰森:哦,好了.
Jason: Oh, OK.
麦琪:杰森.
Maggie: Jason.
杰森:只是开玩笑,麦琪.行了!有虚幻的朋友也不是什么害羞的事情.研究表明几乎所有有创造性的人都有虚幻的朋友.
Jason: Just kidding, Maggie.Come on!It's not anything to be ashamed of having an imaginary friend.Studies show that almost all creative people have had one.
麦琪:啊,我没有.
Maggie: Well, I didn't.
杰森:也许,"朋友"这词重了.也许,只是和你讲话的虚幻的人.
Jason: Maybe, "friend" is too strong a word.Maybe, imaginary person that you talked to.
麦琪:不是.
Maggie: No.
杰森:不是?一种植物.
Jason: No?A plant.
麦琪:不是.
Maggie: No.
杰森:也许一种动物.
Jason: Maybe an animal.
麦琪:噢!
Maggie: Oh!
杰森:你是否曾经有个蚂蚁场,麦琪?
Jason: Have you ever had an ant farm, Maggie?
麦琪:杰森!别说了.我不明白和一个游戏节目主持人说话使得人具有Jason,别说了,我可不明白跟一个电视知识竞赛主持人谈话是怎么让人变得具有创造性的.
Maggie: Jason!Just save it.I fail to see how talking to a game show host, makes one creative.
杰森:哦,好了,进被窝,然后我会告诉你你赢了什么.你去哪儿?
Jason: Oh, well, come under the covers and I'll show you what you've won!Where are you going?
麦琪:我想看看二号门后面有什么.
Maggie: I prefer to see what's behind door number two.
杰森:嗨,布德,我们是在哪里看到那胎记的?
Jason: Hey, Bud, where were we when we saw that mole?
麦琪:哦,有人吃光了奶酪.
Maggie: Well, somebody ate all the cheese.
克莉丝:不,你先.
Chrissy: No, after you.
杰森:你好,小甜心,今天早上感觉怎么样?
Jason: Hi sweetheart, how are you doing this morning?
克莉丝:很好.
Chrissy: I'm great.
麦琪:早餐需要点什么,克莉丝?
Maggie: What would you like for breakfast, Chrissy?
克莉丝:麦片,鸡蛋,吐丝面包,烤薄饼,华夫饼干,面包…..
Chrissy: Oatmeal, eggs, toast, pancakes, waffles, bread...
杰森:哇,哇,哇.是克莉丝还是本?
Jason: Wow, wow, wow.Is that Chrissy or Ben?
克莉丝:他认为,这都是我的.
Chrissy: He thinks, it's all for me.
麦琪:小甜心,你在跟谁说话呢?
Maggie: Sweetheart, who are you talking to?
克莉丝:(尖叫)
Chrissy: (Screams)
麦琪:怎么了?
Maggie: What?
克莉丝:你差点压扁他!
Chrissy: You almost smooshed him!
麦琪:我差点压扁谁?
Maggie: I almost smooshed who?
克莉丝:对不起,艾克.她一直坐这那的.
Chrissy: Sorry about that Ike.She always sits there.
杰森:哦,我明白了.这就是艾克.嗨,艾克,你怎么样?麦琪,跟艾克打招呼.
Jason: Oh, I get it.This is Ike.Hey, Ike, how you doing?Maggie, say hello to Ike.
麦琪:哦,你好,艾克?对此我感觉不舒服.
Maggie: Oh, how do you do, Ike?I'm not very comfortable with this.
克莉丝:艾克说,哎呀,你看起来真年轻!
Chrissy: Ike says, holy moly, you look so young!
麦琪:哦,一个女人从来不会对来自啮齿动物的赞美感到厌烦的.
Maggie: Oh, well, a woman never gets tired of hearing that from a rodent.
哦,谢谢.
Oh, thank you.Do you like my blouse?
你喜欢我的衬衫吗?我认为这能显示出我头发的美丽.
I think it brings out the highlights in my hair.Thank you.
谢谢.你是只非常可爱的老鼠.
You are a very nice mouse.
克莉丝:妈妈,他去洗手间了.
Chrissy: Mom, he went to the bathroom.
麦琪:哦,洗手间.
Maggie: Oh, the bathroom.
杰森:你冲马桶了?
Jason: Did you flush the toilet?
开萝尔:是的,别问我这样的问题.
Carol: Yes, stop asking me that.
克莉丝:开萝尔,这是艾克的椅子.
Chrissy: Carol, this is Ike's chair.
开萝尔:艾克.
Carol: Ike.
麦琪:他坐在这吃早饭
Maggie: He's here for breakfast.
克莉丝:不,现在不在这.他在洗手间.
Chrissy: Not now he isn't.He's in the bathroom.
开萝尔:跟我同时在那里!
Carol: While I was in there!
麦琪:开萝尔!
Maggie: Carol!
克莉丝:艾克和我出去玩了.
Chrissy: Ike and I are going outside to play.
麦琪:好的,亲爱的,你早饭……我叫你,你和艾克的早饭准备好的时候我叫你们.
Maggie: OK, honey, I'll call you when your break...I'll call you and Ike when your breakfast is ready.
克莉丝:好的.快点,艾克.
Chrissy: OK.Come on Ike.
开萝尔 :你真为他准备早餐?
Carol: Are you really gonna cook him breakfast?
杰森:当然不.他是虚幻的.
Jason: Of course not.He's imaginary.
开萝尔:哦,我就不明白你们会和她玩到什么程度.
Carol: Well, I just didn't know how far you'd go to humour the little nut bar.
本:你们知道不知道你的女儿在车道上自言自语?
Ben: Did you know your daughter's in the driveway talking to herself?
开萝尔:不,她在和她的虚幻朋友说话.
Carol: No, she's talking to her imaginary friend.
本:虚幻朋友!
Ben: Imaginary friend!
杰森:是呀.就像你和萨姆海盗.
Jason: Yeah.Like you and Pirate Sam.
本:萨姆海盗不是真实的?
Ben: Pirated Sam wasn't real?
杰森:他对你是真实的,然后你长大就忘记他了,本.
Jason: He was to you, and then you outgrew him, Ben.
本:他告诉我他要出海了.我去躺下了.
Ben: He told me he had to ship out.I gotta go lie down.
麦琪:杰森,克莉丝在那里一个劲的说话.
Maggie: Jason, Chrissy is doing an awful lot of talking out there.
杰森:好的,布德,我们该对这样的妻子做些什么?
Jason: OK Bud, what are we gonna do about the wife?
麦琪:好,好,我知道我没什么好担心的.
Maggie: OK, OK, I know I've got nothing to worry about.
开萝尔:那么如果没有人需要我,我就拿着垃圾在路边.
Carol: Well if anybody needs me, I'll be sitting on the curb with the trash.
杰森:行了,麦琪!克莉丝知道现实和虚幻的区别的.如果她不知道,我们得担心.
Jason: Come on, Maggie!Chrissy knows the difference between real and pretend.If she didn't then we'd have to worry.
克莉丝:我们有进口啤酒吗?
Chrissy: Do we have any imported beer?
麦琪:给艾克的?
Maggie: For Ike?
克莉丝:是的.
Chrissy: Yeah!
麦琪:没有.
Maggie: Forget it.
克莉丝:对不起,艾克,他们说健康食品对你更有好处.
Chrissy: Sorry, Ike, they said something healthy was better for you.
艾克:他们担心我的健康,然而却在家里到处布下了陷阱.我不明白.身体健康.
Ike: They're worried about my health, yet they're setting traps all over the house.I
don't get it.Salut
杰森:嗨,我走了.
Jason: Well, I'm off.
麦琪:好的,亲爱的,一天愉快.去看看病吧.
Maggie: OK, honey, have a good day.Go forth and cure.
杰森:你没事吧?
Jason: Are you alright?
麦琪:这只是个玩笑.
Maggie: It was a joke.
杰森:我是说克莉丝和……你知道的,艾克.
Jason: I was referring to Chrissy and...you know, Ike.
麦琪:哦,亲爱的,你提醒我了.我们之前已经经历过了.
Maggie: Oh, honey, you're reminding me.We've been through all this before.There's absolutely nothing to worry about.
杰森:拜拜,亲爱的,一天愉快.
Jason: Bye bye honey, have a nice day.
艾克:我会的,亲爱的.
Ike: I will dear.
麦琪:克莉丝,该上学了.
Maggie: Chrissy, time for school.
艾克:哦,不,我要离开我!
Ike: Oh no, you're leaving me!
克莉丝:妈妈,艾克就没有人玩了.
Chrissy: Mom, Ike's not gonna have anyone to play with.
麦琪:他不会的.这样……也许艾克希望和你一起去.
Maggie: He won't.Well...maybe Ike would like to come with you.
克莉丝:艾克,你想和我一起上学吗?
Chrissy: Ike, do you wanna go to school with me?
艾克:哦,是呀!
Ike: Oh, yes!
克莉丝:他想去.
Chrissy: He'd love to go.
麦琪:很好.瞧,我可以处理这事.我其他孩子是非常正常的.
Maggie: Wonderful.See, I can handle this.My other children turned out perfectly normal.
开萝尔:你就拿了我的垃圾就走了!我觉得太习惯了.
Carol: You just take my trash and leave!I feel so used.
艾克:啊,哇,很好的邻居关系.
Ike: Ah, wow, nice neighbourhood.
克莉丝:我们喜欢.
Chrissy: We like it.
麦琪:我们喜欢什么,亲爱的?
Maggie: We like what, honey?
克莉丝:邻居关系.
Chrissy: The neighbourhood.
艾克:什么,她是聋子?
Ike: What, is she deaf?
克莉丝:有时候.
Chrissy: Sometimes.
麦琪:有时候,什么呀?
Maggie: Sometimes, what?
艾克:告诉她没有什么.
Ike: Tell her to forget it.
克莉丝:没有什么,妈妈.
Chrissy: Forget it, Mom.
麦琪:好的.
Maggie: OK.
克莉丝:想唱歌吗,艾克?
Chrissy: Wanna sing a song, Ike?
艾克:好呀,你说对了.
Ike: Yeah, you bet.
克莉丝:哪首歌好?
Chrissy: What's a good song?
麦琪:怎么样……滴答,滴答,钟声响?
Maggie: How about...Hickory, Dickory, Dock?
艾克:听着,我拒绝唱这首小老鼠怕小捕鼠器.下一首.
Ike: Look, I refuse to sing a song about a weenie little mouse who's afraid of a little tick-tock.Next.
克莉丝:那么"溪谷里的农夫"?
Chrissy: How about The farmer in the Dell?
麦琪:呵,滴答,滴答,钟声响怎么不好了?
Maggie: Ooh, what was wrong with Hickory Dickory Dock?
克莉丝:你使艾克生气了.
Chrissy: You're upsetting Ike.
艾克:好了,但是当我们唱到那部分,耗子吃了奶酪,为了兄弟,我希望改成老鼠.
Ike: OK, but when we get to the part about, the rat takes the cheese, in honour of the brothers, I'd like to make it a mouse.
克莉丝:我知道了.还有……(唱歌)溪谷里的农夫……
Chrissy: You got it.And...(singing) The farmer in the dell...
艾克:大声一点!克莉丝和艾克一起唱 溪谷里的农夫,嗨嗬,                                                                           牛奶场 哦,溪谷里的农夫.
Ike: A little louder!Chrissy and Ike singing together: The farmer in the dell, hi ho, the dairy o, the farmer in the dell.
麦琪:我可以加入吗?
Maggie: Can I join you guys?
克莉丝:当然.
Chrissy: Sure.
一起:(唱歌)老鼠吃了奶酪,老鼠吃了奶酪……
Together: (singing) The mouse takes the cheese, the mouse takes the cheese...
麦琪:嗨嗬,牛奶场 哦,耗子吃了奶酪!我唱错了吗?
Maggie: Hi ho, the dairy o, the rat takes the cheese!Am I doing it wrong?
克莉丝:你怎么问这个问题,妈妈,当艾克和你一起唱,他对于耗子有什么感受呢?
Chrissy: How can you ask that, Mom, when Ike shared with you how he felt
about rats
艾克:啊,你知道,她讨厌我.这种事情一直发生在我身上.太困难了,做一只美国老鼠.
Ike: Ah, you know, she hates me.This happens to me all the time.It's tough being a rodent American.
麦琪:小甜心,你知道现实和虚幻的区别吗?
Maggie: Sweetheart, do you know the difference between really real and...make-believe?
克莉丝:当然知道.虚幻就是蝙蝠侠.
Chrissy: Of course I do.Make-believe is Bat man.
麦琪:对.
Maggie: Right.
克莉丝:而真正的现实是圣诞老人.
Chrissy: And really real is Santa Claus!!
艾克:那么,这是学校!
Ike: So, this is school!
克莉丝:是的.跟着我,我会告诉你比利 奥尼尔在什么地方让自己难堪的.
Chrissy: Yes.Follow me, I'll show you where Billy O'Neill embarrassed himself.
麦琪:好的.
Maggie: OK.
克莉丝:不是你,妈妈,艾克.
Chrissy: Not you, Mom, Ike.
麦琪:哦.
Maggie: Oh.
老师:麦琪,一切都好?
Teacher: Maggie, is everything alright?
麦琪:当然.我是说,你为什么这么问?
Maggie: Of course.I mean, why do you ask?
老师:是这样,就因为从你看克莉丝的方式.
Teacher: Well, just because from the way you were looking at Chrissy...
麦琪:克莉丝没有什么问题.她十分正常.
Maggie: There is nothing wrong with Chrissy.She is perfectly normal.
老师:我知道.
Teacher: I know.
麦琪:我是说,她正常,是吗?我是说,我不希望从你那里听到不正常.我是说,我明白她正常.我是个好父母,而你只是个老师.不,不,不.我是说,只是一个老师,我是说……
Maggie: I mean, she is normal, right?I mean, not that I need to hear that from you.I mean, I can see that she's normal.I'm a good parent and you're just a teacher.No, no, no.I didn't mean, just a teacher, I meant...
老师:你想来分享圈讨论这些叫做感觉的东西吗?
Teacher: Would you like to come to the share circle and discuss these things called feelings?
麦琪:哦,不,谢谢,萨莉.我真的……得走了.但是现在我在这,克莉丝有做什么事情吗,说些什么……比如老鼠.
Maggie: Oh, no thanks, Sally.I really...have to be going.But while I'm here, has Chrissy been doing anything, talking about anything...mouse-like.
老师:让我想想.哦,她有一天用花生酱黄油三明治去交换奶酪三明治.你是不是担心什么?什么事情让你从镇上到这里?
Teacher: Let me think.Well, she did trade her peanut butter sandwich for a cheese
sandwich the other day.Is something worrying you?
What's taking you to frown town
麦琪:哦,不……没什么……我没什么好担心的.没有提及,说,关于一个六英尺的老鼠,叫艾克.
Maggie: Oh, no...nothing...I have nothing to worry about.No mention, say, of a six foot mouse named Ike.
老师:没有.
Teacher: No.
麦琪:但是她一直在说六英尺老鼠.
Maggie: But she has been talking about a six foot mouse!
老师:没有.
Teacher: No.
麦琪:哦,好.今天待会见.萨莉,你是否认为有一个虚幻的朋友是……恩……有害?
Maggie: Oh, well.See you later today then.Sally, do you think having an imaginary friend is...errm...harmful?
老师:哦,这不好说.你的虚幻朋友是谁?
Teacher: Well, that depends.Who's your imaginary friend?
麦琪:不是我!克莉丝.
Maggie: Not me!Chrissy.
老师:她有个虚幻朋友;很好.
Teacher: She's got an imaginary friend; that's wonderful.
麦琪:是吗?
Maggie: It is?
老师:噢,当然,是有创造性的强烈信号.
Teacher: Well, sure, it's a great sign of creativity.
麦琪:我听说了.
Maggie: I've heard.
老师:而且这可以有时可以满足他们在生活中因为太小而说不清楚的需要.
Teacher: And it can sometimes fill a need in their life that they're too
young to articulate.
克莉丝:妈妈在如此烦恼什么呢?你们大家伙知道吗?
Chrissy: What's my Mom so upset about?Do any of you guys know?
老师:也就是说,她没有得到足够的注意.也许某人忽视她.你们家有叫艾克的吗?
Teacher: It means, she isn't getting enough attention.Maybe someone's ignoring her.Have you got an Ike in family?
麦琪:没有,我们家有本,开萝尔,而且我们还有迈克.迈克,艾克.哦.
Maggie: No, we've got a Ben and a Carol, and we've got a Mike.Mike.Ike.Oh.
艾克:我可以动一下吗,我的尾巴抽筋了?
Ike: Can I move, I'm getting a cramp in my tail?
克莉丝:一点痘不能动,我还没有完成.
Chrissy: Don't move a whisker, I'm not finished.
迈克:你说什么呢?
Mike: What'd you say?
克莉丝:没有什么.我想你会喜欢的.
Chrissy: Nothing.I think you're gonna like this.
本:她变的古怪了.我喜欢.
Ben: She's getting weird.I like it.
麦琪:迈克,再次谢谢你留在家里照看克莉丝.
Maggie: Mike, thanks again for staying home to watch Chrissy.
迈克:哦,嗨,谢谢你先付钱给我.
Mike: Oh, hey, thank you for paying me in advance.
麦琪:而且如果你和克莉丝晚上一起玩的开心的话,她可以迟点睡觉……你知道,八点,九点,十点……午夜.无论什么时候.
Maggie: And if you and Chrissy are having fun together tonight, she can stay up a little later...you know, eight, nine, ten...midnight.Whatever.
本:为什么不是开萝尔照看?
Ben: Why isn't Carol babysitting?
迈克:她和那个垃圾工再次约会了.
Mike: She got another date with the garbage man.
本:她约会!
Ben: She does!
迈克:是的.不要惊讶,本.我是说,那些是靠收垃圾为生的.
Mike: Yeah.Don't be surprised Benny.I mean, those guys take out trash for a living.
艾克:他照看,有意思.
Ike: He is fun to watch.
克莉丝:最好.
Chrissy: The best.
杰森:露西,我回来了.
Jason: Lucy, I'm home.
麦琪:好,迈克,你照看克莉丝.
Maggie: OK, Mike, you keep an eye on Chrissy.
迈克:好的,妈妈.一定会.
Mike: OK, Mom.Sure will.
麦琪:还有本,恩……走开.
Maggie: And Ben, err...go away.
杰森:哇!真漂亮!什么场合?
Jason: Wow!Don't you look nice!What's the occasion?
麦琪:哦,我带你出去吃晚饭.
Maggie: Well, I am taking you out to dinner.
杰森:好呀.
Jason: OK.
麦琪:那么,走吧,走吧,走吧.
Maggie: So, let's go, let's go, let's go.
杰森:什么场合?
Jason: What's the occasion?
麦琪:我们要站在这里回答二十个问题吗?难道就不能出去庆祝相爱的欢乐吗?
Maggie: Well do we have to stand here and play twenty questions?Can't we just go out and celebrate the joy of loving each other?
杰森:好.
Jason: OK.
麦琪:现在抹去你脸上愚蠢的表情.我们走吧.
Maggie: Now wipe that stupid look off your face.And let's move it.
杰森:哦,我有一些事情,今天我在办公室追踪了一些小事情,尽管我应该有空余时间.有关于虚幻朋友的一些研究.你可能发现这些能使你安心.
Jason: Oh, I had a few things, just odds and ends that I tracked down at the office today, you know, while I had some spare time.Just some research about imaginary friends.You might find it kind of reassuring.
麦琪:很好,亲爱的.
Maggie: Great honey.
杰森:你在干什么?
Jason: What are you doing?
麦琪:哦,你是对的,你是对的.我们可以使用便签纸的背面.
Maggie: Oh, you're right, you're right.We can use the back for scratch paper.
杰森:不,麦琪,
Jason: No, Maggie, come on!
行了!
Now here I was trying to ease your mind,
现在我正试着让你放松,
and I come home to discover you're not worried at all.
但是我回家却发现你一点也不担心.你怎么回事?
What's the matter with you?
麦琪:哦,亲爱的,你会感觉好点,如果我哭的话?
Maggie: Oh, honey, would you feel better if I got all weepy?
杰森:不,那不是我需要的.我不希望你那么脆弱和依赖.
Jason: No, that's not what I'm after.I don't want you all weak and needy.
麦琪:哦,甜心,我今天什么都没做对.我在克莉丝老师面前出了洋相,现在我想做的就是带你去吃晚餐.
Maggie: Oh, sweetheart, I can't do anything right today.I made a fool out of myself with Chrissy's teacher and all I wanna do is take you dinner.
杰森:亲爱的,我们可以去吃晚餐.
Jason: Honey, we can go to dinner.
麦琪:真的?
Maggie: Really?
杰森:是的.
Jason: Yes.
麦琪:哦,好.走吧,快点!
Maggie: Oh good.Let's go, come on!
杰森:也许你能关注一下这些事情,在吃甜点或其他东西.
Jason: Maybe you could take a look at these over dessert or something.
迈克:哇,哇,哇!克莉丝,我在楼下就能听到了!你在干什么?
Mike: Wow, wow, wow!Chrissy, I can hear you all the way downstairs!What are you doing?
克莉丝:这是艾克的主意.
Chrissy: It was Ike's idea.
迈克:哦,是的.妈妈告诉我有关艾克的事情.
Mike: Oh, yeah.Mom told me about Ike.
艾克:哦,哦!
Ike: Oh oh!
迈克:现在,听着.你最好告诉艾克,如果他不希望有麻烦的话……同样,我要亲自告诉他.他在哪?
Mike: Now listen.You better tell Ike that if he doesn't wanna get in trouble that...Ditto, I'll tell him myself.where is he?
克莉丝:就在那.
Chrissy: Right over there.
迈克:哦.嗨,艾克!
Mike: OK.Hey Ike!
艾克:是.
Ike: Yes.
迈克:别跳上床.那边.我希望我没有粗暴的对他.
Mike: Don't jump on the bed.There.I hope I wasn't too rough on him.
克莉丝:他活该.
Chrissy: He had it coming.
艾克:他活该!
Ike: He did!
克莉丝:迈克,想和我们玩吗?
Chrissy: Mike, wanna play with us?
迈克:是,是,当然.你们在玩什么呢?
Mike: Yeah, yeah, sure.What are you guys playing?
克莉丝:你想玩什么?
Chrissy: What do you wanna play?
迈克:呃……我喜欢"茶话会".
Mike: Err...I kind o' like Tea Party.
克莉丝:茶话会,好.听起来不错,对我而言.
Chrissy: Tea Party, sure.Sounds good to me.
艾克:嗨!
Ike: Hey!
克莉丝:安静,艾克.
Chrissy: Chill out, Ike.
迈克:是,安静,艾克.把他们竖起来,我要两块糖.
Mike: Yeah, chill out, Ike.Set 'em up and I'll have two lumps.
艾克:是!我想给他两块糖.
Ike: Yeah!I'd like to give him two lumps.
克莉丝:艾克,坐下,别像个孩子.
Chrissy: Ike, sit down and stop being a baby.
艾克:我不想.
Ike: I don't wanna.
克莉丝:好.坐在那,就那样.
Chrissy: Fine.Stay there, be that way.
迈克:没有什么比老鼠有想法更糟了.小子,咖啡是热的.
Mike: Nothing worse than mouse with an attitude.Boy, this coffee's hot.
克莉丝:是茶.
Chrissy: It's tea.
艾克:哈!
Ike: Ha!
迈克:在燃烧着的老鼠夹的火光中,老鼠先生意识到,他再也没有什么可害怕的了.最终,多年的游荡结束了.他最后还是回家了.结束.
Mike: And in the glow of the fire of the burning mouse traps, Mr.Mouse realised he had nothing to fear ever again.Finally, the years of wandering were over.He was home at last.The end.
迈克和艾克:哦,哇,好故事!
Mike and Ike: Oh, wow, good story!
克莉丝:你和艾克真的很像.
Chrissy: You and Ike are a lot alike.
迈克:是呀,哪里像?我们的鼻子.
Mike: Yeah, what is it?Our noses.
艾克:哦,它可以夹东西吗,你呢?
Ike: Oh, can it cute stuff, will you?
克莉丝:你们不象.但是你们都有趣.我喜欢和你们玩.
Chrissy: You don't look alike.But you're both funny.I like playing with you guys.
迈克:是,我也喜欢和你玩,克莉丝.
Mike: Yeah, I like playing with you too, Chrissy.
克莉丝:你喜欢!
Chrissy: You do!
迈克:是.别那么震惊.我是说,如果我不是经常这样做的话,这……哦有时我也喜欢和大女孩玩.
Mike: Yeah.Don't sound so shocked.I mean, if I don't do it all the time it's...well sometimes I like playing with the big girls too.
克莉丝:像,昨晚.
Chrissy: Like, last night.
迈克:对.哦,你知道,就如你知道的那样.我今晚会免费照看你的.
Mike: Right.Well, you know, just so you know, I would have babysat you for free tonight.
克莉丝:真的?
Chrissy: Really!
艾克:哦,大英雄.
Ike: Oh, big hero.
迈克:嗨,克莉丝,明天,我去给我的车打蜡,你能帮我吗?
Mike: Hey, Chrissy, tomorrow, I'm gonna wax my car, you wanna help me?
克莉丝:真的!
Chrissy: Really!
迈克:哦,好.
Mike: Oh, yeah!
克莉丝:你要能让我碰你的车!
Chrissy: You'd let me touch your car!
艾克:真烦人.
Ike: This is boring.
迈克:七点整……早晨!
Mike: Seven O' clock sharp...am!
克莉丝:你会起那么早!
Chrissy: You're getting up that early!
迈克:不.你.我八点三十需要用车,然后我可以带你去吃早饭.
Mike: No.You are.I need the car by eight thirty so I can take you to breakfast.
克莉丝:行!
Chrissy: Alright!
迈克:好.行,进被窝!睡觉吧.好.好好睡,金发.明早见.
Mike: OK.Alright, under the covers!Here you go.Good.Sleep tight, Goldie locks.See you in the morning.
艾克:好,在我们被无礼中断之前,我们在哪?
Ike: OK, where were we before we were so rudely interrupted?
克莉丝:艾克,睡觉啦.
Chrissy: Ike, it's bed time.
艾克:哦,失败者现在睡觉!快点!我们玩.
Ike: Oh, bed time's for losers!Come on!Let's party.
克莉丝:我在帮迈克,早上很早,清楚吗?
Chrissy: I'm helping Mike, early in the morning, remember?
艾克:哦,因此你说,你宁愿明天给迈克的车打腊,而不是现在和我玩.
Ike: Oh, so you're saying you'd rather detail Mike's car tomorrow, rather than to play with me now!
克莉丝:艾克,我要睡觉了
Chrissy: Ike, I gotta go to sleep.
艾克:哦,好吧!好,那么,我想自己玩"茶话会".
Ike: Oh, well fine!OK, well, I wanted to play Tea Party by myself anyway.
克莉丝:好的.
Chrissy: OK.
艾克:我在做什么?我是只长大的老鼠.
Ike: What am I doing?I'm a grown mouse.
杰森:什么,所以在克莉丝学校你把所有的事情都说了.
Jason: What, so you put all this together at Chrissy's school.
麦琪:没有,但是这样做有意义.克莉丝的确对迈克有英雄崇拜.
Maggie: No, but it does make sense.Chrissy does have this hero worship thing for Mike.
杰森:是,那是真的.
Jason: Yeah, that's true.
麦琪:因此,也许如果他们更多的时间在一起,她就不需要艾克.
Maggie: So, maybe if they spend more time together, she won't need Ike.
杰森:亲爱的,我讨厌把你归到专业一类,但是我怀疑一晚上在一起会让艾克有什么不同.
Jason: Honey, I hate to pull professional rank on you, but I doubt if one evening together's gonna make any difference with Ike.
艾克:是呀,你说的对.
杰森:你说什么了吗?
00:22:14,300
Ike: Yeah, says you. Jason: Did you say something?